[
    {
        "question" : "C is the successor of ___ programming language.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "C++",
            "B++",
            "B",
            "Mini C"
        ],        
        "answer" : "B"
    },
	{
        "question" : "How to round-off a value '5.77' to 6.0?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "ceil(5.77)",
            "round-off(5.77)",
            "round-up(5.77)",
            "floor(5.77)"
        ],        
        "answer" : "ceil(5.77)"
    },
	{
        "question" : "stderr, stdin, stdout are FILE pointers.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],        
        "answer" : "True"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which library functions help users to dynamically allocate memory?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "memalloc()and alloc()",
            "malloc() and memalloc()",
            "malloc() and calloc()",
            "memalloc() and calloc()"
        ],        
        "answer" : "malloc() and calloc()"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Identify the invalid constant used in fseek() function as ‘whence’ reference.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "SEEK_SET",
            "SEEK_CUR",
            "SEEK_BEG",
            "SEEK_END"
        ],        
        "answer" : "SEEK_BEG"
    },
	{
        "question" : "The keyword used to transfer control from a function back to the calling function is",
        "options" : 
        [
            "switch",
            "goto",
            "go back",
            "return"
        ],        
        "answer" : "return"
    },
	{
        "question" : "The library function used to find the last occurrence of a character in a string is",
        "options" : 
        [
            "strnstr()",
            "laststr()",
            "strrchr()",
            "strstr()"
        ],        
        "answer" : "strrchr()"
    },
	{
        "question" : "The first argument to be supplied at command-line must always be count of total arguments.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],        
        "answer" : "False"
    },
	{
        "question" : "How will you free the allocated memory ?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "remove(var-name);",
            "free(var-name);",
            "delete(var-name);",
            "dalloc(var-name);"
        ],        
        "answer" : "free(var-name);"
    },
	{
        "question" : "malloc() allocates memory from the heap and not from the stack.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],        
        "answer" : "True"
    }
]